What was my first fulcrum?
私の最初の支点は何でしたか？
The mesenteric artery.
腸間膜動脈です。
First fulcrum, one.
最初の支点、一つ目。
Second fulcrum,
二番目の支点、
the left colic flexure, it is fixed.
左結腸曲は固定されています。
Third fulcrum,
三番目の支点、
I am deep here.
私はここに深部にいます。
And the last point,
そして最後の支点は、
is here.
ここです。
So my intestine, in fact, does this.
ですから、私の腸は実際にはこう動きます。
In the opposite direction.
逆方向に。
I place myself there, and in fact the movement is like this.
私はそこに位置し、実際には動きはこのようなものです。
Do you see what I mean?
私が何を言いたいか分かりますか？
I am now entering a tissue of motility.
今、私は運動性組織に入ります。
I can begin to trace a history.
私は物語を辿り始めることができます。
I am immediately drawn to the stomach, the spleen, and the left colic flexure.
私はすぐに胃、脾臓、そして左結腸曲に引き寄せられます。
Its fulcrum is occupied.
その支点は占有されています。
to rebalance a rather deep psychic plane.
かなり深い精神的な平面を再均衡化する。
Perhaps it is still searching for another fulcrum.
もしかしたら、彼はまだもう一つの支点を探しているのかもしれません。
We will bring it to a more anterior fulcrum.
我々は彼をより前方にあるフルクラムへ導きます。
It will rediscover information in its dreams.
彼は夢の中で情報を見つけるでしょう。
It is in this balance between this aortic plane and this
彼はこの大動脈平面と脾臓平面の間のバランスの中にいます。
splenic plane.
それは、表面に戻ろうとしている無意識の統合の平面です。
It is a plane of integration, of the unconscious that wants to return to the surface
そして夢の形、あるいは悪夢の形で表現され得ます。
and which can express itself as a dream or a nightmare.
私はそれを左側に置きます。
I place it on the left side.
支点を得るため、ここにこの自由を得るために。
to have a fulcrum, to have this freedom here.
そして、最終的な支点はここに置かれます。
And then, the final point is placed here.
通常、上腹部緊張は下腹部緊張よりわずかに高いべきです。
Normally, the epigastric tension should be slightly greater
Normalement,  la  tension  épigastrique  doit  être  légèrement  supérieure
than the hypogastric tension.
à  la  tension  hypogastrique.
Always a search for abdominal normotension or abdominal hypotension.
常に腹部正常張力または腹部低張力の探求を行います。
In my palpation, if the hypogastric tension is superior to
私の触診において、下腹部張力が
my epigastric tension,
私の上腹部張力を上回る場合、
I am rather in a system of...
私はむしろ〜のシステムにあると言えます。
Then either I must work within a system of viscerospatial rebalancing or
その場合、私は内臓空間的再均衡のシステムで対処するか、
fluidic.
または体液のシステムで対処する必要があります。
Anything that is hypertension, I must release the fluids.
高張力がある場合は、体液を再解放しなければなりません。
Anything that is in hypotension, I have a slackening.
低張力がある場合は、弛緩が見られます。
Therefore, I must reintegrate the viscerospatial system, meaning I must restore the dynamics, increase
したがって、内臓空間システムを再統合する必要があります。つまり、ダイナミクスを再付与し、
the force.
活力を増加させる必要があります。
This entire ascending colon here, normally, there are still small excesses,
ここにある上行結腸全体には、通常、わずかな過剰があり、
small dietary verdicts, can still be improved.
食事に関するわずかな問題も、まだ改善の余地があります。
let's say. When I ascend here, I have an angle that goes like this and I descend again, I descend
と言えるでしょう。ここを上ると、このような角度があり、そして私は降りていき、
into my zone of joy or, if not resolved, into the zone
喜びの領域、あるいはそれが解決されていない場合は、
of my anger. When I descend here,
私の怒りの領域へと降りていきます。ここを降りると、
the transverse colon here, it represents my certainties in life or, if
ここにある横行結腸は、私の人生における確信を表します。あるいは、もし
I have not
私がそれらを
resolved them, my doubts. When I ascend here,
解決していない場合は、私の疑念を表します。ここを上ると、
I represent, the ascent here represents the zone
私は表します、ここを上ることは、
of confidence.
信頼の領域を表します。
or of my anxieties.
あるいは私の不安の領域を表します。
The angle zone here, it is called the culprit's burden.
ここにある角度の領域は、「罪悪感の足かせ」と呼ばれます。
The culprit's burden, that's what needs to be released.
この罪悪感の足かせこそ、取り除くべきものです。
Here, it's the entire zone here, then when I descend again here,
ここは、この領域全体であり、そして私がここを降りていくと、
I call that the search for my independence.
私はそれを私の独立性の探求と呼びます。
I must be totally free from my parents.
私は両親から完全に自由でなければなりません。